You want to know what we're doing today?
Going on the first hike of the year.
I've done this hike before.
It's called the Tunnel Bluffs, and it's located in Horseshoe Bay, Vancouver.
I did it with my friend Gemma last year.
It was really nice.
It's long, but it's not super crazy strenuous, so I feel like it's a really
good hike to start off the hiking season and I'm excited about it.
It's looking like this is what I'm wearing.
This hat is from my mom.
This top is azure fit and these shorts are literally just thrifted which is awesome.
They're like the perfect hiking shorts.
They're really comfortable.
They have a lot of pockets and then I just got these wool socks on
that I got yesterday when I bought my hiking shoes.
Then we got some sunglasses too.
These are literally just from shoppers drug mart.
Okay now it's time to pack the bag.
First off I'm not gonna put this in my backpack but I I am gonna
bring my bathing suit and towels because it's gonna be hot and afterwards if I
want to go for a swim, I'm ready and prepared.
So also bringing two towels, but these are not going in my bag.
I packed up my bag with all of the necessities and I also decided to
bring my sketchbook.
So I decided to bring my sketchbook because I actually want to get more into
sketching and doing little drawings and art whenever I go on hikes or go outside
or even just like going to the art gallery or something.
And so I recently took this class on Skillshare, which has been helping me a
lot with getting better at drawing and sketching because it's definitely not my forte.
It's called Basic Skills Getting Started with Drawing.
The class touches on how to get started using basic shapes to create drawings and
how to shade and finish things up.
I have a basic knowledge of drawing because throughout elementary and high school I took
a few art classes but it was nice to have a solid refresher because I
honestly do not remember a lot of the things that I learned then.
The class also had so many great tips and tricks that really helped me improve
my drawing.
I also really liked being able to take things at my own pace, which which
Skillshare always allows you to do.
And another cool thing about it is that you can actually take a class from
anywhere.
If you want to download classes and take them offline, you can.
So honestly, if I wanted to learn how to draw on the top of a
mountain, I could do that as well.
Overall, Skillshare is a great place to learn a creative skill or pick up a
new hobby.
If you're looking to reconnect with your creativity this summer, Skillshare is where people go
to learn from other people.
And if you want to check it out, you can either scan the QR code
or click the link in my description and the first 500 people to do so
will get an entire month free.
I made these little protein balls the other day, so I think I'm literally just
gonna pack two of these.
Do you want to go and get a sandwich?
So that'll be my my snacks for the trip.
Okay, let's go.
The hiking shoes that I'm wearing today Are these I just got them yesterday and
I need to break them in before I go to Peru.
They're Salman I don't know what type but I'm just gonna wear my Burke's while
I drive so first stop of the day is I'm gonna go get a sandwich
because I Love having a sandwich at the top sandwich with a view.
It's my favorite thing to do.
Wow that rhymes Anyway, first we're gonna get a sandwich and then we're gonna go
to the hiking location.
And it's a bit of a drive but whatever so let's go
we've arrived at the sandwich location now let's go get a sandwich for the hike
we got a pesto chicken sandwich i'm really excited about it do i want to
eat it now yes but I have to wait until we finish the hike or
at least get I mean get to the viewpoint of the hike.
So now straight to the hiking location.
First hike of the year.
Freaking joyful.
Okay so we have arrived.
Had to park a little bit far.
okay
we got the hiking boots on they feel nice and good and secure i've set
my parking to like four hours but uh yeah i'm gonna set out on the
hike i'm excited it's literally such a beautiful day and i can't wait to get
up on the trail except i kind of can wait because the first two kilometers
are literally straight uphill.
So that's not the most pleasant thing ever.
Wow, the hike hasn't even begun and it's already beautiful.
And I also need to pee.
Luckily, there's a bathroom at the trailhead.
Okay, we made it to the trailhead.
But actually, it was like a three-minute walk, so not bad at all.
you guys first viewpoint the porta potties
okay so we only have a kilometer and a half left of this horrendous uphill
and then it's pretty much flat after that.
I'm going to need to stop for a water break soon.
I am sweating significantly.
Okay, beautiful.
We have reached two kilometer mark finally.
So we're done two kilometers.
Oh, now it's time for some water.
I'm actually sweating so much.
I wore a cotton bra.
I'm like, shouldn't have done that.
I am like sitting right in the sun, so that was a poor choice.
Oh, bug in my nose.
I think now I'm just gonna not listen to music and give myself a little
bit of time to think and reflect.
Cause that's actually what I love about hiking is that it's peaceful and relaxing and
it gives you time to really like think.
Okay, now there are bugs swarming me cause I'm sweaty.
So I should probably get moving.
Okay, so that lighting was literally
awful.
Also, side note, I love these shorts.
I literally got them thrifting, and they're awesome.
Even though they're long, they're super nice and light, and they literally fit perfectly.
So excited.
I'll have to do this one sometime this summer.
The Lions.
The Lions or something.
That one's like a multi-day, I think.
But I'd love to do that.
I need to start getting comfortable doing this stuff by myself.
I think the first step is going camping alone.
I'm so excited now it's literally flat from here and I can like power walk.
I've like immediately cooled off also because now I'm not walking straight uphill in the
sun.
The first stream crossing.
Luckily, these babies are Gore-Tex.
Got the bridge crossing coming up.
I will not be recording this.
I do not want to fall in the river.
Okay bridge hiked.
Time to eat my peanut butter ball.
Three kilometers.
I'm getting ready for my sandwich.
Almost
there.
So now that we've made it to the top, it's time to eat our sandwich.
Okay, the sandwich has been opened.
Oh, okay.
Wait, this looks beautiful.
I'm so excited to eat it.
It feels a little bit soggy, but it's also been in my backpack for like
two hours.
So that makes sense.
Look at that.
That is so good.
so sandwich review it's really good
it has this like pesto mayo so it's not just like pesto it's a pesto
mayo which is really good and then it has arugula which i love arugula in
a sandwich a little aged cheddar and then some sun-dried tomatoes just like literally so
scrumptious as for the gluten-free bread i feel like it's like this is pretty basic
gluten-free bread this is what I usually use like it's nothing special.
Points could be added if the bread was like a soft focaccia but that is
the struggle of being gluten-free sometimes so yeah but otherwise very good.
I also brought my sketchbook so I'm gonna go to like the main viewpoint and
do a little sketch because I want to start sketching things that I find beautiful.
Thank you.
我们 下 期 再见 好 棒 啊 太 棒 了 现在 回 到 沙 滩
可能 会 花 我 一 小 小 的 时间 但 我 花 了 很多 时间
在 那 块 岛 上 很 漂亮 的 地方 试 着 做 一个 绘 画
需要 绘 画 但 我 现在 想 要 去 泳 因为 很 热 沙 滩
很 近 然后 我 朋友 们 和 所有 女 士 们 在 那 边 做
个 小 烧 烤 就是 ...
這 就是 我 夢 想 的 夏 天 這是 我的 夢 想 我的 夢 想
騎、 溜 冰、 烤 肉 天 啊 還有 更 新 一下 這些 鞋 子 我的
腳 很 熱 但是 鞋 子 真的 很好 他們 給 我 很多 支 援 我
遇 到 一些 河 流 沒有 把 我的 腳 水 流 進 去 所以 很好
我 喜歡 它 目前 沒有 被 爆 破 這 就是 最 重要 的 事情 我
穿 的是 夏 天 的 冬 裙 所以 它 们 比 较 厚 和 暖
和
这 会 比 较 好 我 去  Peru   时 因为 它 们 会 比
较 冷 但 目前 来 说 它 们 肯 定 比 较 热 但 这
也是 我 自己 选 择 的 但 没有 什么 问题 我 肚 子 很 舒
服 所以 很好 我 真的 喜欢 这 些 鞋 子 我觉得 我 今天 可以 穿
更 多 的 日 式 鞋 但是 我 需要 把 这 些 裙 子 弄
进 去 因为 你 不 想 你的 第一 次 在 鞋 子 上 的 鞋
子 就 像 是 五 天 的 旅 程 我
认 为 我 需要 设 定 一个 目 标 我 需要 做 至 少 一
周 的 一 周 的  hike 它 们 不 必 太 大 但是 在 曼
谷 和 西 方 的 地方
有 很多  hike   要 做
所以 我 必 须 去 那 里 去 探 索 它 有 很多 事情 要
看 和 做 10 公 里 完成 了 我 认 为 我们 现在 还有 两
个 现在, 所以 我 其实 已经 在 上 山 了 我 超 期 待 下
山 的 那 一 段 真的 会 很 棒 现在 是 下 山 了 我
总 是 找 到 下 山 是 最 难 的
快 完成 了 我们 完成 了 好了, 回 到 车 里 了 我的 腿 已经
有 点 疼 了 现在 是 时候 把 我的 浴 袋 放 上 去, 去
上 山 了
我們 在 海 灘, 我 穿 著 我的 泳 衣 我們 走吧
优 优 独 播 剧 场 —— Yo Yo  Television  Series  Exc lusive